<?xml version="1.0"?>
<root>
  <continent>
    <name>Europe</name>
    <discription>&#xD;
        There simply is no way to tour Europe and not be awestruck by its natural beauty, epic history and dazzling artistic and culinary diversity. &#xD;
        Europe&#x2019;s almost unmanageable wealth of attractions is its biggest single draw: the birthplace of democracy in Athens, the Renaissance art of Florence, the graceful canals of Venice, the Napoleonic splendour of Paris, and the multilayered historical and cultural canvas of London. Less obvious but no less impressive attractions include Moorish palaces in Andaluc&#xED;a, the fascinating East-meets-West brew of &#x130;stanbul in Turkey, the majesty of meticulously restored imperial palaces in Russia's former capital St Petersburg and the ongoing project of Gaud&#xED;'s La Sagrada Fam&#xED;lia in Barcelona.&#xD;
    </discription>
    <countries>
        <country>
            <name>Italy</name>
            <discription>&#xD;
                Home to many of the world's greatest works of art, architecture and gastronomy, Italy elates, inspires and moves like no other.</discription>
            <image>../../images/italy.jpg</image>
            <link>https://www.lonelyplanet.com/italy</link>
        </country>
        <country>
            <name>Greece</name>
            <discription>&#xD;
                Hedonists rejoice! Greece is ancient sun-bleached ruins piercing blue skies, the balmy Aegean lapping an endless coastline and a culture alive with passionate music, wonderful cuisine and thrill-seeking activities.            </discription>
            <image>../../images/greece.jpg</image>
            <link>https://www.lonelyplanet.com/greece</link>
        </country>
        <country>
            <name>Norway</name>
            <discription>&#xD;
                The essence of Norway's appeal is remarkably simple: this is one of the most beautiful countries on earth.&#xD;
            </discription>
            <image>../../images/norway.jpg</image>
            <link>https://www.lonelyplanet.com/norway</link>
        </country>
        <country>
            <name>France</name>
            <discription>&#xD;
                France seduces travellers with its unfalteringly familiar culture, woven around cafe terraces, village-square markets and lace-curtained bistros with their plat du jour (dish of the day) chalked on the board.&#xD;
            </discription>
            <image>../../images/france.jpg</image>
            <link>https://www.lonelyplanet.com/france</link>
        </country>
    </countries>
  </continent>
</root>
